You have recently wondered what are your rights about free credit report.
Are you entitled to a free credit report.
Whatever.
Hello I'm Robert Todd and I'm here to answer what is the law about free credit reports.
As you know employers often and are allowed by law to check your credit report for their background checks for you with regards to both perspective employment and with existing employment.
The United States Fair Credit Reporting Act entitles you as an individual to receive a free credit report once a year.
Now there are a lot of websites that talk about sending you the free credit report and so forth, beware.
Instead I would site you to annual credit report dot com to receive your free credit report.
And pay attention to your credit report, it's probably not a bad idea to check on this once a year.
I'm Robert Todd and thank you for watching.